Finding Aid for the Pacific Palisades Property Owners Association Records LSC.0874
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Maps
  - Brentwood/Palisades Community Plan - Plan map., n.d. (Box 91)
  - Brentwood/Palisades Community Plan - Open space and public lands Santa Monica Mountain area. (Box 91)
  - Brentwood/Palisades Community Plan - General plan - Status map., 1974 September 17 (Box 91)
  - Brentwood/Palisades Community Plan - Zoning redesignations., n.d. (Box 91)
  - Brentwood/Palisades Community Plan - Land use west Los Angeles., 1990 December (Box 91)
  - Two traffic profile maps., 1982 (Box 92)
  - Six school administrative area maps., Various dates (Box 92)
  - Certificate of Good Show (hand drawn)., 1961 June 9 (Box 92)
  - TT 32184 (hand drawn). (Box 92)
  - Los Angeles area., n.d. (Box 92)
  - Two Acquisition Priority for Santa Monica Mountains maps., n.d. (Box 93)
  - Four Pacific Coast Highway bike path maps., n.d. (Box 93)
  - Palisades highlands - Fire Station Park - Planting Plan., 1990 June 21 (Box 93)
  - Five proposed plan maps - Brentwood/Pacific Palisades., 1976 March (Box 93)
  - Open space and recreation - Brentwood/Pacific Palisades., 1977 December (Box 93)
  - Mountain Park properties., 1972 February (Box 93)
  - Oil drilling districts - Los Angeles., n.d. (Box 93)
  - Triunfo pass quadrangle., n.d. (Box 93)
  - Topanga State Park - Mott's map., n.d. (Box 93)
  - Palisades highlands photo aerial. (Box 94)
  - Forty-one Palisades maps., n.d. (Box 94)
  - Palisades Village commecial specific plan., 1992 November (Box 94)
  - United States Geographical map for Palisades and Topanga. (Box 94)
  - Hand drawn map of a ridge. (Box 94)
  - Palisades highlands - Gateway - Master plan. (Box 94)
  - Topanga SP - Lazard holdings., n.d. (Box 94)
  - Fourteen miscellaneous plan and profile maps - Santa Monica City boundary to Station 11., 1979 (Box 95)
  - Topanga Park (hand drawn). (Box 95)
  - Palisades highlands - Revised tentative map. (Box 95)
  - AMH/Watt [?] - 40 lot study., n.d. (Box 95)
  - AMH/Watt - Preliminary studies for modified 21601., n.d. (Box 95)
  - Marquez Canyon / Sunset - Headlands mitigation. (Box 96)
  - Acquisition priorities for Santa Monica Mountains., n.d. (Box 96)
  - Pacific Coast Highway - Santa Monica City line to Temescal., n.d. (Box 96)
  - Four Palisades precinct maps., n.d. (Box 96)
  - Marquez Canyon / Sunset., n.d. (Box 96)
  - Marquez Canyon [?]., n.d. (Box 96)
  - Nine Brentwood / Pacific Palisades zoning maps., n.d. (Box 96)
  - Three Topanga State Park proposed acquisiont Palisades Heights area maps., n.d. (Box 96)
  - Two McClure / Temescal traffic profile maps., 1982 (Box 96)